Hello everyone.
This is Moeko Kanizawa and
Nanaka Tomita of Not Equal Me
Hi!
This time
Yakiniku!
This is the third time!
Isn't this crazy?
I'm so happy.
I think we're getting older.
What a surprise.
The first time was at Gyukaku.
All-you-can-eat! One more time!
The first time was all-you-can-eat at Gyukaku.
It brings back memories.
And the second time, on the way back from a location shoot in Karuizawa.
We had delicious, delicious yakiniku.
It was a reward from a reward, wasn't it?
Thumbnail?
That's right! When I got the script, there was a thumbnail.
When I got the script, you laid out the thumbnails like this.
You can feel the history.
Do you do it every year?
Yes, about every year.
Two years ago? This year?
Wow!
You've grown up.
Not much has changed?
My hair length has changed.
I tie mine up and let it down.
I tied mine both ways today.
This time, we're here at Ushigoro's.
Mr. Ushigoro!
Did you come?
Me too!
Did you try it?
I'd like to go there, wouldn't you? I'd like to go there, wouldn't you?
We're in the neighborhood.
I saw your website and everything.
I'm really looking forward to it.
That's right. So this time, too.
I'd like to eat yakiniku while chatting loosely.
So I'd like to have a BBQ dinner while chatting loosely with you all.
Let's eat!
Bon appétit!
Thank you very much.
Here's the menu.
It even lists the parts of the meat.
I hear a squeal.
It's a sound theory.
Stop. Don't drink.
There are four kinds of tongue.
Which tongue?
Which one do you want?
What do you like?
Moego-Tan...
Let's ask him what he recommends.
Let's do that.
Nokolagen komtan soup.
That's good.
I like the egg soup.
I'll have the egg soup. Shall we decide on the drinks?
Ginger ale or corn?
Ginger ale or corn, I guess. We're always together.
Ginger ale for me.
Ginger ale, then.
Yes, please.
Do you have any suggestions for a tang?
Well, I'd have to say... the ultimate low tongue.
Well, thickness.
That's what I'll have.
I'm so hungry!
I'm empty now too even now it's empty
Oh, sorry.
Hmm?
Oh!
Oh, right.
I had to take care of something.
I finished too early.
I found Bon Blanc on the corner.
I got a head start on dessert.
It's so tiny! It's so tiny!
Oh, my God.
Shall we have a toast?
Yes, everyone, do you have your glosses on hand?
Do you have any gloss on hand?
We're working hard.
Cheers.
Yay!
That's cool.
It was really hot today.
Delicious!
Today's topic is
Manaka-chan
We celebrated your birthday the other day!
Happy birthday!
The other day?
I thought maybe that's where the meat came from, but I got distracted and left the other day behind.
Yes, it's true. I had a birthday. Thank you.
Yes, it's been a year since we've done this.
This time, we're celebrating your birthday, too.
Like a birthday.
It's true, I haven't done it yet.
I was with her the day before her birthday.
We went to karaoke.
At the drink bar.
I told her I was going to get a drink, and then I was gone. I told him I was going to get a drink and then I was gone.
When he came back, he brought me
Veron soda and lemon scotch in the color of my penlight
and wished me a happy birthday.
I don't know if that's possible.
And I was like, “Well, I guess I can have one or the other.
I wanted a lemon squash.
So I got the yellow lemon squash.
Then I wanted yellow corn soup.
It was cold.
I had the air conditioner on.
I got the corn soup.
It's my birthday.
He went to get it for me.
Every year on my birthday, I have to go to work or something.
Member.
Because of work and stuff.
I was with him more often than not, so I used to say happy birthday to him then, but this year...
But this year, I was off.
I was off.
I thought I wouldn't see you this year, but then I got a message on LINE from everyone
Happy Birthday!
Mi-chan sent me another happy birthday song with a voice memo.
I want to play it now
Happy Birthday J.Y.J. Happy Birthday
I want to go on the floor with you
It's called Happy Motors
A log belterben
I like
Cute
He's the first one.
So cute.
He arrived at exactly 12:00.
He said it's my birthday again this year.
They all gave me a birthday present.
I'm so happy.
Happy birthday to you.
Looks delicious! looks delicious!
Congratulations!
Oh, YUKKE is here!
YUKKE is here!
Ta-da-da-da!
Bon appétit!
Yum!
It's so thick!
It's yamoruri!
It doesn't show
I'm happy because I'm in a period of holding back on meat.
After all, lately, when I'm choosing my meals...
I've been holding off on the meat, caramel, and other things I've been eating for today, just for today.
Bon appétit!
I'm going to eat...
It's about 5 cups of rice.
I want to drink this yukke live!
I really want to make it my drink of choice at the concert.
It's really bad!
I know what you mean.
It's nice to know.
It's like a dance block or something.
Freshness, freshness, freshness
more than usual.
Kanaka and Mayuko
like they're in high spirits.
You might say they certainly had a lot of power.
Tour?
I thought it would be nice to talk about how the tour went... for the first time in Kagoshima.
That's right. In the early days, we started talking about how we wanted to do a show in Kagoshima.
It's been 5 years. I'm so glad.
I'm so glad. And then Kagoshima came up on the screen.
And then when Kagoshima came up on the screen, I screamed like crazy. I screamed so hard that day.
That's right.
I was so surprised that I couldn't go to Okinawa.
But now I wonder if it was foreshadowing.
When they showed the announcement video, I was like “boo hoo” when they said we might be able to go to Okinawa. When they showed the announcement video, they said “boo-boo” to the guy who said he might be able to go to Okinawa.
He said he couldn't go.
The timing of the Nakaoka concert was unexpected, but for us, the announcement was a surprise.
I was so surprised.
We wanted to go to Okinawa, and Chiba, and we're so happy that we'll be able to go to the extra shows.
You know...
I'm crying so hard.
Everyone's crying.
And seeing myself crying so hard, I realized that I didn't want the tour to end like this.
I know...
It was a school trip, right?
The school trip is in Kagoshima, so it ends in the middle of Kyushu
I see.
Elementary school, junior high school, and high school are different...
I've heard about school trips to Okinawa.
I heard from my friends and kids from other schools that they went on a school trip to Okinawa.
I was so happy to hear that.
I'm so happy that it's going to come true this time!
I'm looking forward to it!
I'm so excited!
We'll all be there. We'll definitely go in the ocean. Is it cold? No, it's not cold.
No, it's not cold. My goal this year is to go to a beautiful beach and pull a boat.
Banana boat? Snorkeling? It'll be snowing.
That's what I thought we'd do this year.
Let's do it.
Oh, it's true. You're pulling.
It's amazing.
Amazing.
I knew it was different.
I raised him.
I'm going to be pissed.
Sparkle.
Sparkles.
Since there seems to be extra rice left over, I will serve it with sauce and egg over it, which is very popular, so please try it if you like.
Thank you very much.
I don't want to leave anything like this behind.
Hey, I shouldn't have done it all at once just now.
Oh, no! It's really bad! Look at this! Wow! It's really bad! Look at this!
Oh no! Oh, man!
Oh, no! This is bad!
It's a big mess.
değer afford Given
Oh no, no, no!
They're disappearing
Don't go away!
I'll take it!
Speaking of good food
The pizza from “Summer is Here” was so good!
I know it's a very aggressive way of bringing it to you, but it was delicious.
The pizza guy came to our place.
That's right.
There are many kinds of pizzas.
He said he recommended the kimchi pizza.
The kimchi pizza was very popular, wasn't it?
I went to get it.
When I went to get it, he said, “I don't think you should go back.
He kindly said, “I'll go back one more time now.
I went back a second time to get it.
It's not there yet?
No, I think it's gone.
Isn't it early?
So fast! That's great.
It hasn't been there for a long time.
The “Pizza Incident”.
The pizza incident.
Hey, since summer is here...
It's been almost a month since the music video was released.
Have you listened to the music video?
Of course I have!
Yay!
I'm so glad you're listening.
It's been like a crazy summer vacation.
We were so close to the ocean.
It was beautiful.
It was beautiful. It was beautiful.
And I had a conversation with one of them.
Oh, yeah.
I talked about how good you are at imitating a Japanese bush warbler.
When I imitated a Japanese bush warbler
and he answered me correctly.
I don't know what he said.
What did you say to him?
Hey!
Is everyone here? I'm here! I'm here! I thought I heard you say, “I'm here!
I had a feeling you were.
You're really good at this.
The making of? Is it on?
I don't know if it was or wasn't, but you'll have to check.
You'll have to wait and see.
If not, I'll be happy to show it to you at a talk session or something.
Thank you.
I've been trying to get the guise of a storyteller for a long time.
I have a friend who might get bored...
But it's a great place, isn't it?
The view was beautiful... and right in front of it was the ocean... the ocean floor...
There's a place where you can see the bottom of the ocean.
We can see from the top or the observation deck.
And there's a scene where they do this. It was so cute.
It was so cute... and then we'd do it like this, like that.
I love the sunset! I love that scene too!
I'm so happy!
It's so elegant.
He lives in the best house in the world, Truffle.
What's that?
It's so close.
Are you into taking pictures up close these days?
We're going to take a close-up and ask you what it is.
Okay, I'll take the quiz first.
Who is this?
Let me see.
Oh, but there's this one above.
The one with the skirt and the top. You know, the kind with the skirt and the top part.
Like Mirei and Momo, the one-piece type that's connected to the skirt.
They're different.
Oh, that's me, isn't it?
That's right.
That's me.
I recognized you from your tie.
There you are.
This is kind of fun.
It's fun.
Wow.
That's a lot.
That's amazing!
I've never had this many truffles before!
Wow, wow, wow!
And the truffles are piled high!
Amazing!
Truffles have been very popular for a while.
There was even a battle of the truffle potato chips!
When it comes to truffle flavor, it's Yumi!
When people see this, they'll all say
We all have to try it together!
Cold noodles!
Cold noodles. This way.
Can you see it? Cold noodles... she puts a lot of vinegar on it.
I'll save some for later. I'll probably use it all.
He'll use it. He'll use it. Will he be shy? Start the quiz, everyone.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
I can't even write this.
Here, I'll give you a little something.
Thank you.
Oh no, oh no, it spilled
Awww!
Did you guys see that?
The correct answer is, “Jalatto.
All the time.
You can write it all down. You could write it all down.
When I went to Reilly's.
I wonder which way it's going to be today.
There's a camera.
Which one is it? Which way is it? We were having a quiz.
The correct answer is...
Kozcuz. - Kozcuz.
It was just a little bit.
It's okay, I can write it all down.
I thought you might be picky.
I thought you might be a little sensitive about it, so I just pushed it all out, and I felt bad about it.
I knew you were being conscientious.
Is that obvious?
Quiz over.
Go home.
How's it going?
Thank you very much.
Happy birthday to you
Oh, shit.
This is the best way to live!
Okay?
Okay, well, try to get there from this distance.
It's not far!
Before you start filming.
Hold it and shake it.
Yes, sir!
Hold it.
Okay, thank you.
Here we go.
Whoo!
Thank you!
Yay!
I'm 24 years old!
Yeah!
I'm 24!
It's the first time I've had a drop
This year. This year
I didn't do it this year.
That's for sure.
That's why.
And my birthday... we celebrated.
I'll give you a drop.
Do you have any aspirations for turning 24?
Twenty-four?
I say this every year.
I'd like to be a little more mature.
Oh, well...
I mean...
Oh, my God, you're going to be an adult.
Can't we?
What?
Yes, you can.
I want to do a lot of new things.
This year, too.
I think so.
I want to never stop challenging myself.
Such a 24 year old
I'm sure you'll be keeping an eye on Nanahi.
Moeko is also one to keep an eye on.
So, with that, I'll see you all
See you all next year.
If you all say yes, we'll do it again next year.
Maybe next year.
It's a yakiniku project.
I'm looking forward to it. Thanks, everyone.
End of page
Please leave a comment or click the “Good” button.
Thank you.
How was your day?
Rhino.
Wow!
Too much!
It's not even a hug. It's not even a squeak.
Mwah.